I O
love O
programming O
in O
Python B-LANG
. O

Machine B-SKILL
learning I-SKILL
is O
fascinating O
. O

Spacy B-TECH
is O
a O
useful O
library O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
a O
versatile O
language O
. O

Named B-TASK
Entity I-TASK
Recognition I-TASK
is O
important O
. O

Google B-ORG
is O
a O
leading O
tech B-INDUSTRY
company O
. O

Elon B-PER
Musk I-PER
is O
the O
CEO O
of O
Tesla B-ORG
. O

The O
COVID-19 B-EVENT
pandemic I-EVENT
has O
impacted O
the O
world O
significantly O
. O

Microsoft B-ORG
was O
founded O
by O
Bill B-PER
Gates I-PER
. O

Apple B-ORG
introduced O
the O
iPhone B-PROD
in O
2007 B-DATE
. O

Amazon B-ORG
is O
a O
global O
e-commerce B-INDUSTRY
giant O
. O

Facebook B-ORG
rebranded O
to O
Meta B-ORG
in O
2021 B-DATE
. O

New B-GPE
York I-GPE
City I-GPE
is O
a O
major O
financial B-INDUSTRY
hub O
. O

SpaceX B-ORG
launched O
the O
Falcon B-PROD
Heavy I-PROD
rocket I-PROD
. O

The O
Olympics B-EVENT
are O
held O
every O
four O
years O
. O

Python B-LANG
and O
Java B-LANG
are O
popular O
programming O
languages O
. O

NASA B-ORG
is O
planning O
a O
mission O
to O
Mars B-LOC
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Wall I-LOC
of I-LOC
China I-LOC
is O
a O
historic O
landmark O
. O

Tesla B-ORG
produces O
electric B-PROD
vehicles I-PROD
. O

The O
Eiffel B-LOC
Tower I-LOC
is O
in O
Paris B-GPE
. O

Google B-ORG
Maps I-PROD
is O
a O
widely O
used O
navigation O
app O
. O

Lionel B-PER
Messi I-PER
is O
a O
famous O
football B-SPORT
player O
. O

The O
stock B-INDUSTRY
market O
can O
be O
volatile O
. O

The O
Academy B-EVENT
Awards I-EVENT
celebrate O
cinematic B-INDUSTRY
achievements O
. O

Jeff B-PER
Bezos I-PER
is O
the O
founder O
of O
Amazon B-ORG
. O

The O
Pacific B-LOC
Ocean I-LOC
is O
the O
largest O
ocean O
. O

The O
Sahara B-LOC
Desert I-LOC
is O
in O
Africa B-LOC
. O

Harvard B-ORG
University I-ORG
is O
an O
Ivy B-INDUSTRY
League I-INDUSTRY
school O
. O

The O
World B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
monitors O
global O
health O
trends O
. O

The O
Wright B-PER
Brothers I-PER
invented O
the O
airplane B-PROD
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
used O
in O
data B-TASK
science I-TASK
. O

The O
Taj B-LOC
Mahal I-LOC
is O
in O
India B-GPE
. O

Tesla B-ORG
is O
known O
for O
its O
electric B-PROD
cars I-PROD
. O

The O
Google B-ORG
search B-TASK
engine I-TASK
is O
widely O
used O
. O

NASA B-ORG
is O
exploring O
space B-LOC
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Barrier I-LOC
Reef I-LOC
is O
in O
Australia B-GPE
. O

The O
United B-GPE
States I-GPE
of I-GPE
America I-GPE
is O
a O
large O
country O
. O

The O
Silicon B-LOC
Valley I-LOC
is O
a O
tech B-INDUSTRY
hub O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
great O
for O
machine B-TASK
learning I-TASK
. O

The O
Sphinx B-LOC
is O
a O
historic O
monument O
in O
Egypt B-GPE
. O

New B-GPE
York I-GPE
is O
a O
busy O
city O
. O

The O
Grand B-LOC
Canyon I-LOC
is O
a O
natural O
wonder O
. O

Python B-LANG
supports O
multiple O
programming O
paradigms O
. O

Amazon B-ORG
Prime I-PROD
offers O
fast O
shipping O
. O

The O
Mona B-PROD
Lisa I-PROD
is O
a O
famous O
painting O
. O

The O
Berlin B-LOC
Wall I-LOC
fell O
in O
1989 B-DATE
. O

Elon B-PER
Musk I-PER
founded O
SpaceX B-ORG
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Lakes I-LOC
are O
a O
group O
of O
five O
large O
lakes O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
used O
for O
web B-TASK
development I-TASK
. O

The O
Rocky B-LOC
Mountains I-LOC
are O
in O
North B-LOC
America I-LOC
. O

Microsoft B-ORG
Office I-PROD
is O
a O
suite O
of O
productivity O
tools O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
popular O
in O
data B-TASK
analysis I-TASK
. O

The O
Golden B-LOC
Gate I-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
is O
in O
San B-GPE
Francisco I-GPE
. O

The O
Big B-LOC
Ben I-LOC
is O
in O
London B-GPE
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
known O
for O
its O
simplicity O
. O

The O
Statue B-LOC
of I-LOC
Liberty I-LOC
is O
in O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Pyramids I-LOC
are O
in O
Giza B-LOC
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
widely O
used O
in O
scientific B-TASK
computing I-TASK
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Barrier I-LOC
Reef I-LOC
is O
in O
Australia B-GPE
. O

The O
Sydney B-LOC
Opera I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
a O
famous O
landmark O
. O

Amazon B-ORG
Web I-PROD
Services I-PROD
is O
a O
cloud B-INDUSTRY
computing I-INDUSTRY
platform O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
used O
for O
AI B-TASK
research I-TASK
. O

The O
Empire B-LOC
State I-LOC
Building I-LOC
is O
in O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Wall I-LOC
of I-LOC
China I-LOC
is O
a O
historic O
landmark O
. O

Google B-ORG
Drive I-PROD
is O
a O
cloud B-INDUSTRY
storage I-INDUSTRY
service O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
known O
for O
its O
extensive O
libraries O
. O

The O
Colosseum B-LOC
is O
in O
Rome B-GPE
. O

Tesla B-ORG
produces O
electric B-PROD
cars I-PROD
. O

The O
United B-ORG
Nations I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1945 B-DATE
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
great O
for O
data B-TASK
visualization I-TASK
. O

The O
Sphinx B-LOC
is O
a O
historic O
monument O
in O
Egypt B-GPE
. O

The O
World B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
monitors O
global O
health O
trends O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
used O
in O
natural B-TASK
language I-TASK
processing I-TASK
. O

The O
Grand B-LOC
Canyon I-LOC
is O
a O
natural O
wonder O
. O

The O
Pacific B-LOC
Ocean I-LOC
is O
the O
largest O
ocean O
. O

The O
Wright B-PER
Brothers I-PER
invented O
the O
airplane B-PROD
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Lakes I-LOC
are O
a O
group O
of O
five O
large O
lakes O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
used O
for O
web B-TASK
development I-TASK
. O

Amazon B-ORG
Prime I-PROD
offers O
fast O
shipping O
. O

The O
Eiffel B-LOC
Tower I-LOC
is O
in O
Paris B-GPE
. O

The O
United B-GPE
Kingdom I-GPE
is O
a O
country O
in O
Europe B-LOC
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
known O
for O
its O
simplicity O
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Pyramids I-LOC
are O
in O
Giza B-LOC
. O

Google B-ORG
Maps I-PROD
is O
a O
widely O
used O
navigation O
app O
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
widely O
used O
in O
scientific B-TASK
computing I-TASK
. O

The O
Berlin B-LOC
Wall I-LOC
fell O
in O
1989 B-DATE
. O

The O
Olympics B-EVENT
are O
held O
every O
four O
years O
. O

Python B-LANG
and O
Java B-LANG
are O
popular O
programming O
languages O
. O

The O
Mona B-PROD
Lisa I-PROD
is O
a O
famous O
painting O
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Barrier I-LOC
Reef I-LOC
is O
in O
Australia B-GPE
. O

The O
Sydney B-LOC
Opera I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
a O
famous O
landmark O
. O

Elon B-PER
Musk I-PER
is O
the O
CEO O
of O
Tesla B-ORG
. O

Microsoft B-ORG
was O
founded O
by O
Bill B-PER
Gates I-PER
. O

The O
Academy B-EVENT
Awards I-EVENT
celebrate O
cinematic B-INDUSTRY
achievements O
. O

The O
Great B-LOC
Wall I-LOC
of I-LOC
China I-LOC
is O
a O
historic O
landmark O
. O

Jeff B-PER
Bezos I-PER
is O
the O
founder O
of O
Amazon B-ORG
. O

The O
Pacific B-LOC
Ocean I-LOC
is O
the O
largest O
ocean O
. O

Lionel B-PER
Messi I-PER
is O
a O
famous O
football B-SPORT
player O
. O

The O
United B-GPE
States I-GPE
of I-GPE
America I-GPE
is O
a O
large O
country O
. O

The O
Silicon B-LOC
Valley I-LOC
is O
a O
tech B-INDUSTRY
hub O
. O

The O
World B-ORG
Health I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
monitors O
global O
health O
trends O
. O

The O
Golden B-LOC
Gate I-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
is O
in O
San B-GPE
Francisco I-GPE
. O

The O
Empire B-LOC
State I-LOC
Building I-LOC
is O
in O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
. O

Python B-LANG
is O
great O
for O
machine B-TASK
learning I-TASK
. O

NASA B-ORG
is O
planning O
a O
mission O
to O
Mars B-LOC
. O

The O
Olympics B-EVENT
are O
held O
every O
four O
years O
. O

The O
COVID-19 B-EVENT
pandemic I-EVENT
has O
impacted O
the O
world O
significantly O
. O